gotohoroscope.com 2013-04-09

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

**The Information We Collect**   
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on our website. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name, Email address, (etc.) 

**How We Use Information**   
We use the information you provide about yourself only to complete a specific request, for example, to post a comment on our blog or to subscribe to our email feed. We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**How We Use Cookies**   
A cookie is a small file placed on your computerâ€™s hard drive that enables us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. Our site and third parties such as advertisers may add a cookie to help analyze web traffic or to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you, however, from taking full advantage of the website. 

**Third-party advertisement**   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.   
For example Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [the Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

Goto [Horoscope](http://www.gotohoroscope.com/) COM
